const quiz = [
    {
        question_id: 1,
        question: "WWW stands for ?",
        question_img: "",
        options: ["World Whole Web", "Wide World Web", "Web World Wide", "World Wide Web"],
        answer: "World Wide Web",
    },
    {
        question_id: 2,
        question: "Which of the following are components of Central Processing Unit (CPU) ?",
        question_img: "",
        options: ["Arithmetic logic unit, Mouse", "Arithmetic logic unit, Control unit", "Arithmetic logic unit, Integrated Circuits", "Control Unit, Monitor"],
        answer: "Arithmetic logic unit, Control unit",
    },
    {
        question_id: 3,
        question: "Which among following first generation of computers had ?",
        question_img: "",
        options: ["Vaccum Tubes and Magnetic Drum", "Integrated Circuits", "Magnetic Tape and Transistors", "All of above"],
        answer: "Vaccum Tubes and Magnetic Drum",
    },
    {
        question_id: 4,
        question: "Where is RAM located ?",
        question_img: "",
        options: ["Expansion Board", "External Drive", "Mother Board", "All of above"],
        answer: "Mother Board",
    },
    {
        question_id: 5,
        question: "If a computer has more than one processor then it is known as ?",
        question_img: "",
        options: ["Uniprocess", "Multiprocessor", "Multithreaded", "Multiprogramming"],
        answer: "Multiprocessor",
    },
    {
        question_id: 6,
        question: "If a computer provides database services to other, then it will be known as ?",
        question_img:"",
        options: ["Web server", "Application server", "Database server", "FTP server"],
        answer: "Database server",
    },
    {
        question_id: 7,
        question: "Full form of URL is ?",
        question_img: "",
        options: ["Uniform Resource Locator", "Uniform Resource Link", "Uniform Registered Link", "Unified Resource Link"],
        answer: "Uniform Resource Locator",
    },
    {
        question_id: 8,
        question: "In which of the following form, data is stored in computer ?",
        question_img: "",
        options: ["Decimal", "Binary", "HexaDecimal", "Octal"],
        answer: "Binary",
    },
    {
        question_id: 9,
        question: "Which level language is Assembly Language ?",
        question_img: "",
        options: ["high-level programming language", "medium-level programming language", "low-level programming language", "machine language"],
        answer: "low-level programming language",
    },
    {
        question_id: 9,
        question: "Documents, Movies, Images and Photographs etc are stored at a ?",
        question_img: "",
        options: ["Application Sever", "Web Sever", "Print Server", "File Server"],
        answer: "File Server",
    }
];

export default quiz;